<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Game Instants</title>
    <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Game Instants</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://gameinstants.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gameinstants.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> General Guide on How to Build in SMITE: Tips and Tricks for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/smite-source-builds/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/smite-source-builds/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this article, we will discuss the general rules of building in Smite, a popular online multiplayer game. Building in Smite involves making strategic decisions about which items to purchase for your character in order to maximize their potential in matches. It&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this guide is not meant to provide specific build guides for each character, as the game is constantly changing and requires a deep understanding of the mechanics and gameplay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> I Found Some Seriously Amazing Characters in Idle Angels</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/idle-angels-tier-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/idle-angels-tier-list/</guid>
      <description>Idle Angels is a popular goddess idol RPG game that has been making waves in the mobile gaming community. In this game, you can summon and collect various characters, each with their own unique abilities and powers. The game has gained a lot of attention for its stunning art style and addictive gameplay mechanics. In this article, we will take an in-depth look at Idle Angels and explore what makes it an amazing game to play.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tekken 2: A Game That Defined the Evolution of the Series</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/tekken-2-tier-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/tekken-2-tier-list/</guid>
      <description>Tekken 2, the sequel to the original Tekken game, marked a significant leap forward for the series. Developed in just one year, Tekken 2 vastly improved upon its predecessor and set the template for future installments. In this article, we will explore the key features that made Tekken 2 stand out and the impact it had on the fighting game genre.
A Battle of Rivals The story of Tekken 2 continues the rivalry between two main characters, Heihachi and Kazuya.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Stream PS4 on Discord: Easy Method</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/ps4-stream-to-discord/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/ps4-stream-to-discord/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will guide you through a simple and easy method to stream your PS4 gameplay on Discord. Streaming your gameplay can enhance your gaming experience and allow you to share it with your friends and community on Discord. By following the steps outlined below, you will be able to seamlessly stream your PS4 on Discord and even allow your friends to hear the in-game audio.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Stream PS4 on Discord: Easy Method for Sharing Gameplay</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/stream-ps4-over-discord/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/stream-ps4-over-discord/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Have you ever wanted to share your PS4 gameplay with friends on Discord? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck because in this article, we will guide you through the easy process of streaming your PS4 on Discord. With just a few simple steps, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to show off your gaming skills and enjoy the experience together with your friends.
Step 1: Visit PS Remote Play Website
To begin, you need to visit the PS Remote Play website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> QUETZAL BREEDING GUIDE - TOP TIPS FOR COLOR MUTATIONS IN ARK SURVIVAL EVOLVED</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/quetzal-mating-ark/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/quetzal-mating-ark/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this guide, we will explore the exciting world of Quetzal breeding and color mutations in Ark Survival Evolved. Quetzals are majestic flying creatures that players can breed to achieve unique and vibrant color variations. We will provide step-by-step instructions and share our experience in obtaining these mutations. Get ready for an adventure filled with 400 Quetzal eggs and the quest to unlock stunning color mutations!
Gathering Stable Bedding Before we dive into the breeding process, let&amp;rsquo;s address a common question: where to find stable bedding?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Shaking Up Teller - A Comprehensive Prapor Task Guide for Escape From Tarkov</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/tarkov-shaking-up-teller/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/tarkov-shaking-up-teller/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling with the &amp;ldquo;Shaking Up Teller&amp;rdquo; task in Escape From Tarkov? Look no further! In this comprehensive guide, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk you through the steps required to successfully complete this task and earn valuable rewards. Follow this guide closely to ensure a smooth and successful completion.
Introduction The &amp;ldquo;Shaking Up Teller&amp;rdquo; task involves obtaining a specific item from dorm room 203 on the Customs map and surviving an extract.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Stream PS4 on Discord: Easy Method</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/stream-ps4-to-discord/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/stream-ps4-to-discord/</guid>
      <description>This article provides step-by-step instructions on how to stream your PS4 gameplay on Discord. By following this easy method, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to share your gaming experience with friends and let them hear the sound coming from your PS4.
Are you looking for a way to stream your PS4 gameplay on Discord? Look no further! In this article, I will guide you through an easy method to showcase your gaming skills and share the exciting sound effects with your friends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Level Zero: The First Preview – A Terrifying Blend of Dead by Daylight and Alien Isolation</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/new-pc-games-like-dead-by-daylight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/new-pc-games-like-dead-by-daylight/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Level Zero is an upcoming asymmetrical survival horror game that draws inspiration from iconic titles such as Dead by Daylight and Alien Isolation. Developed by Dog Howl Games, this game combines intense PvP gameplay with elements of teamwork and strategic thinking. In a recent hands-off preview, I had the opportunity to witness the thrilling gameplay and get a taste of what Level Zero has to offer.
The Storyline and Gameplay Level Zero takes players on a science expedition gone wrong, where four scientists find themselves pitted against two powerful monsters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PP-19 Bizon: Exploring Gaming&#39;s Most Popular SMG</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/pp-19-smg-gfl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/pp-19-smg-gfl/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:
In the world of video gaming, there are many iconic weapons that have captivated players over the years. One such weapon is the PP-19 Bizon, a submachine gun (SMG) that has gained popularity among gamers. In this article, we will delve into the details of the PP-19 Bizon, its design, features, and its role in gaming. Join us as we explore the fascinating world of this unique SMG.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Jump Force in 2023: A Nostalgic Look Back on the Definitive Manga Fighting Game**</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-jump-force-cross-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-jump-force-cross-platform/</guid>
      <description>[Image]
Welcome back to Retro Rebound! In today&amp;rsquo;s video, we&amp;rsquo;re diving back into the world of Jump Force. Released in 2019, Jump Force promised to be the ultimate anime fighter, combining characters from 15 different manga series. With iconic characters like Goku, Naruto, and JoJo all in one game, expectations were high for this crossover extravaganza. However, fast forward to 2023, and the game&amp;rsquo;s support has dwindled, leaving fans wondering if Jump Force still holds up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Play Crossplay with Your Friends on Hunt Showdown (Xbox One) (PS4)</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/hunt-showdown-crossplay-xbox-ps4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/hunt-showdown-crossplay-xbox-ps4/</guid>
      <description>H1
Introduction In this article, we will discuss how to play crossplay with your friends on Hunt Showdown for Xbox One and PS4. Crossplay refers to the ability for players on different platforms to play together in the same game. Hunt Showdown is a multiplayer first-person shooter game that offers crossplay functionality, allowing players on Xbox One and PS4 to team up and play together. Many players have been trying to figure out how to play with friends on different platforms, and we have the solution for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Stream Xbox Games on Discord: A Gamechanger for Xbox and Discord Integration</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-stream-xbox-games-on-discord/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-stream-xbox-games-on-discord/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In a groundbreaking move, Microsoft has announced an improvement to the Discord on Xbox integration. Now, gamers can finally stream their gameplay directly to their friends on Discord. This new feature enhances the already existing Discord voice chat integration on the Xbox dashboard, creating an immersive and interactive gaming experience. In this article, we will guide you step by step on how to stream your Xbox gameplay to your Discord channel and explore the exciting possibilities it offers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Get the Perfect Mouse Aim: A Comprehensive Guide to Mouse Sensitivity and Settings</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/modern-warfare-2019-aim-converter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/modern-warfare-2019-aim-converter/</guid>
      <description>Mouse sensitivity and DPI settings are critical factors in achieving precise aim and accuracy in any FPS game. But converting sensitivity between games and understanding the impact of FOV (Field of View) can be challenging. In this guide, we will explore the best practices for setting up your mouse sensitivity, converting sensitivity between games, and optimizing other important mouse settings. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or an experienced gamer, this article will help you achieve the perfect mouse aim for maximum performance in modern warfare games, particularly in the highly acclaimed game, Modern Warfare 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Copy Your Sensitivity to Any Game with Kovaak&#39;s Sensitivity Matcher</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-sensitivity-to-rainbow-six-siege/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-sensitivity-to-rainbow-six-siege/</guid>
      <description>Discover the simple yet powerful tool for copying your sensitivity settings from one game to another
Are you a gamer who struggles with adjusting to new sensitivity settings when switching between games? Introducing Kovaak&amp;rsquo;s Sensitivity Matcher, a free and reliable app developed by Cal Vox Kovac, a trusted name in the gaming community. Gone are the days of manually adjusting your sensitivity for each game. With this app, you can easily copy your sensitivity and ensure a seamless experience across different games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Stream Xbox Games to Discord: A Step-by-Step Guide for Xbox Users</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-stream-xbox-games-to-discord/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-stream-xbox-games-to-discord/</guid>
      <description>Microsoft has recently introduced an integration between Xbox and Discord, allowing players to stream their gameplay directly to their friends on Discord. This exciting new feature has been highly anticipated by gamers, and in this article, we will guide you through the process of streaming Xbox games to your Discord channel.
Step 1: Enable Discord Voice Chat Integration Before you can start streaming your gameplay, you need to ensure that Discord voice chat integration is enabled on your Xbox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> MUSTY Rocket League Settings 2021: Achieve SSL 3v3 Success | Expert Tips and Tricks</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/musty-camera-settings/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/musty-camera-settings/</guid>
      <description>Rocket League is a popular and competitive game that requires skill, strategy, and the right settings to succeed. In this article, we will be discussing the musty camera settings and gameplay settings used by Musty, a professional Rocket League player. By analyzing his settings and gameplay, we can gain valuable insights into how to improve our own Rocket League performance.
Introduction to the MUSTY Rocket League Settings 2021 Rocket League is a game where every little detail matters, including camera settings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Uber Atziri - Alluring Abyss: Path of Exile - A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/mortal-grief-poe/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/mortal-grief-poe/</guid>
      <description>Overview In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll be discussing the Uber Atziri boss fight in Path of Exile&amp;rsquo;s Alluring Abyss. We&amp;rsquo;ll explore the mechanics of the fight and provide a step-by-step guide on how to successfully defeat Uber Atziri. This guide is aimed at Path of Exile players who are looking to challenge themselves and experience one of the game&amp;rsquo;s most difficult encounters. We&amp;rsquo;ll also discuss the key points and strategies to keep in mind during the fight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Difference in 1st Edition, Shadowless &amp; Base Set Pokemon Cards: A Complete Guide</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/shadowless-pokemon-card-vs-pokemon-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/shadowless-pokemon-card-vs-pokemon-card/</guid>
      <description>Written by: [Your Name]
Introduction In the world of Pokemon cards, there are various versions of the base set that collectors and enthusiasts should be aware of. This article will provide an in-depth analysis of the three main versions of the base set: unlimited, shadowless, and first edition shadowless. By understanding the differences between these versions, collectors can make informed decisions when buying and selling Pokemon cards.
First Edition Shadowless The first version to consider is the first edition shadowless set.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HOW TO CONVERT YOUR SENSITIVITY BETWEEN GAMES: A Simple and Reliable Method</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-sensitivity-converter/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-sensitivity-converter/</guid>
      <description>As gamers, we often find ourselves switching between different games, each with its own unique settings and sensitivities. This can be frustrating, especially if you have found the perfect sensitivity in one game and want to replicate it in another. Fortunately, there is a simple and reliable method to transfer your sensitivity from one game to another, ensuring a consistent and optimal gaming experience across different titles.
Download Aimlab for Accurate Sensitivity Conversion To begin this process, you will need to download a free game called Aimlab from Steam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Every 4-Star SMG in Girl&#39;s Frontline: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/girls-frontline-best-characters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/girls-frontline-best-characters/</guid>
      <description>Girl&amp;rsquo;s Frontline is a popular strategy game that has captured the hearts of many players. With a wide range of characters to choose from, it can be overwhelming to decide which ones are the best. In this article, we will be focusing on the 4-Star SMGs in the game and discussing their strengths, weaknesses, and overall usefulness.
PB90: A Beginner&amp;rsquo;s Trap PB90 is a shiny new 4-Star SMG that may attract the attention of new players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Stream PS4 on Discord: Easy Method</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/stream-ps4-discord/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/stream-ps4-discord/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a way to stream your PS4 gameplay on Discord? Look no further! In this article, we will guide you step by step on how to achieve this and impress your friends with your gaming skills. With a few simple steps, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to showcase your PS4 gameplay on Discord and even allow your friends to hear the in-game sounds. So let&amp;rsquo;s get started!
Before we delve into the process, make sure you have at least 32 likes on this video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Escaping from Tarkov: Gunsmith Part 21 Quick and Easy - 0.13.0 Patch</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/escape-from-tarkov-ab-arms/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/escape-from-tarkov-ab-arms/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will be discussing Gunsmith Part 21 in the popular video game Escape from Tarkov. This particular mission is unique as it features two weapons, the Colt M1911A1 and the Remington Model 700. We will provide a step-by-step guide on how to complete this mission easily and quickly. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive right into it!
The Colt M1911A1 - A Classic Pistol The first weapon we will be working on is the Colt M1911A1, a .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Conan Exiles Crossplay Now Available: Play with PS4, PC, and Xbox Players! [RoxGames]</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-conan-on-ps4-cross-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-conan-on-ps4-cross-platform/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of playing Conan Exiles on your own platform and missing out on the opportunity to connect and play with friends on other devices? Well, we have some exciting news for you! In a recent live broadcast by Funcom, they discussed the implementation of cross-platform play for Conan Exiles. This means that players on PC, PS4, and Xbox can now join forces and play together on shared servers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Concord: Understanding Grammatical Concord or Subject-Verb Agreement</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/concord-error/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/concord-error/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will delve into an essential aspect of grammar known as &amp;ldquo;Concord&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;Subject-Verb Agreement.&amp;rdquo; Concord plays a crucial role in ensuring the coherence and clarity of sentence structure. In English, it is vital to make sure that the verb is appropriately conjugated according to the subject. Failure to maintain proper concord can result in grammatical errors that can confuse readers or listeners. Let&amp;rsquo;s explore the rules and nuances of concord to help you develop a strong grasp of this fundamental grammar concept.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Start the Wish-Ender Quest: An Easy Updated Exotic Guide for 2023!</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-start-the-wish-ender-quest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-start-the-wish-ender-quest/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Are you ready to embark on the journey to obtain the Wish-Ender bow in Destiny 2? The Wish-Ender is an outstanding exotic bow, and with the recent changes made by Bungie, the quest to obtain it has become much simpler and less complicated. In this article, we will break down the steps and changes made to the Wish-Ender quest, ensuring that you have all the information needed to successfully obtain this powerful exotic weapon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> So I Tried Playing JUMP FORCE In 2023: An Unforgettable Experience</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/jump-force-crossplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/jump-force-crossplay/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In today&amp;rsquo;s digital age, video games have become a significant part of popular culture. One game that attracted significant attention upon its release in 2019 was JUMP FORCE. Developed by Bandai, JUMP FORCE offered an exciting and unique experience, bringing together 15 different manga franchises into one game. With characters from beloved series such as Dragon Ball, Naruto, and One Piece, JUMP FORCE had the potential to become the definitive manga fighting game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Mega Blastoise EX &amp; Blastoise EX PSA 10: Unboxing Rare Pokémon Cards</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/mega-blastoise-ex-psa-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/mega-blastoise-ex-psa-10/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be unboxing and exploring the Mega Blastoise EX and Blastoise EX PSA 10 graded cards from the Pokémon Evolutions set. These cards, purchased by James Burns Vlogs, hold great value and are highly sought after by collectors. We will delve into the details of these cards, their significance, and the uniqueness of the set they belong to.
Unboxing PSA 10 Graded Cards James Burns Vlogs is back with another exciting unboxing video, where he unveils rare Pokémon cards that have been professionally graded by PSA.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Convert Your Sensitivity from Fortnite to CS:GO [2021 Tutorial]</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-to-csgo-sens/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-to-csgo-sens/</guid>
      <description>In the world of gaming, many players often switch between different games. However, transferring the sensitivity settings from one game to another can be a difficult and time-consuming task. This tutorial will guide you on how to easily convert your sensitivity from one game to another, specifically from Fortnite to CS:GO. By following these steps, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to maintain the same level of precision and accuracy in both games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Stream Xbox Gameplay to Discord: An Exciting New Feature</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/stream-xbox-games-on-discord/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/stream-xbox-games-on-discord/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:
Microsoft is constantly improving the integration between Xbox and Discord to enhance the gaming experience for its users. One of the recent updates they have rolled out is the ability to stream your Xbox gameplay directly to your friends on Discord. This feature has been eagerly awaited by gamers, and now it is finally here. In this article, we will explore how you can stream Xbox gameplay to your Discord channel, the customization options available, and what to expect in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Boys Are Back Again &amp; They&#39;re Flaming - Fire Based Double Strike Zerker</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/dual-strike-poe/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/dual-strike-poe/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will be discussing a unique and powerful build in Path of Exile (POE), known as the &amp;ldquo;Flaming Boys&amp;rdquo; build. This build revolves around the Double Strike skill, which allows players to create clones of themselves that attack using the same skill. With the right setup and gear, players can create an army of melee destruction, making this build incredibly powerful.
The Concept of the &amp;ldquo;Boys&amp;rdquo; The term &amp;ldquo;the boys&amp;rdquo; refers to the vile Double Strike portion of the build, where players create clones of themselves that attack with Double Strike as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Xenoverse 2 PS4 &amp; Xbox One Crossplay: A Game-Changing Possibility</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/xenoverse-2-crossplay-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/xenoverse-2-crossplay-2022/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In a recent announcement by Sony, they revealed that they are now giving developers the opportunity to enable crossplay for their games. This means that players on different gaming platforms, such as PS4 and Xbox One, can finally play together. While this news is exciting for gamers in general, it begs the question: Should Xenoverse 2, one of the popular anime games, embrace this feature? In this article, we will dive into the pros and cons of implementing crossplay in Xenoverse 2 and explore the potential impact it could have on the gaming community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ESPN Reporter Malika Andrews Secretly Dating White NBA Reporter Dave McMenamin: Rumors and Reactions</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/malika-andrews-dating/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/malika-andrews-dating/</guid>
      <description>In a surprising turn of events, ESPN reporter Malika Andrews has been outed for allegedly secretly dating her co-worker, Dave McMenamin. The news has been buzzing all over social media, with fans and followers expressing their shock and amusement at the revelation. This article will delve into the rumors, explore their origins, and discuss the reactions surrounding this unexpected relationship.
The Background Malika Andrews gained her fame as a talented journalist and host of ESPN&amp;rsquo;s NBA Today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> I Tried Out The New Crossplay on Insurgency Sandstorm: A Game-Changing Update</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/insurgency-sandstorm-xbox-one-crossplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/insurgency-sandstorm-xbox-one-crossplay/</guid>
      <description>Insurgency Sandstorm, a popular first-person shooter game, has recently introduced a game-breaking new update that includes cross-platform play between PC and Xbox players. This unexpected update has been met with both excitement and confusion among the gaming community. In this article, we will dive into the details of this update, how it works, and the player experience.
Crossplay and Mouse and Keyboard Support
The highlight of this update is the introduction of cross-platform play, allowing PC and Xbox players to compete against each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> In-Depth Guide on How to Identify Shadowless Pokemon TCG Cards from Unlimited Cards</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/shadowless-pokemon-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/shadowless-pokemon-cards/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Are you a fan of collecting Pokemon Trading Card Game (TCG) cards? If so, you may have come across the terms shadowed and shadowless cards. Shadowless cards, especially the first editions, hold a special rarity in the world of Pokemon TCG card collecting. But how can you differentiate between shadowed and shadowless cards? In this article, we will delve into the details of identifying shadowless Pokemon TCG cards from unlimited cards, providing you with step-by-step instructions and key pointers to help you become an expert at identifying these valuable cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Win Gomoku: Learn the Winning Strategy and Dominate Every Connect 5 Game</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-win-gomoku/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-win-gomoku/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of losing every Connect 5 game? Do you want to learn the winning strategy that will help you dominate your opponents? Look no further, because in this article, we will reveal the secret to winning every single Connect 5 game. By avoiding one crucial mistake, you can secure victory in just nine moves. So, strap in and get ready to unleash your Connect 5 skills!
The Black Hole Strategy The key to winning Connect 5 lies in understanding the &amp;ldquo;Black Hole&amp;rdquo; strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Make Your Minecraft Skin Glow and Stand Out!</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/aura-minecraft-skin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/aura-minecraft-skin/</guid>
      <description>In Minecraft, having a unique and eye-catching skin is important for standing out in the game. But what if you could take it one step further and make your skin glow? Imagine the possibilities! In this article, we will show you how to use the Custom Player Models mod to make your eyes or any other part of your body glow. Get ready to make your Minecraft skin 10 times cooler!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Where to Watch NBA Games Free: Explore All Options!</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/nbastreams-xyz-live-stream-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/nbastreams-xyz-live-stream-sports/</guid>
      <description>by SmashCut!
Are you a basketball enthusiast looking for ways to catch NBA games without spending a dime? We&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered! In this article, we will explore multiple methods that allow you to watch NBA games for free. Whether you are based in the United States or reside outside the country, we have something for everyone. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive right in and discover the most convenient option for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **5 BEST Da Hood Script GUIs in Roblox: Aimlock, ESPs, and More (2023 Pastebin)**</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/da-hood-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/da-hood-script/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for the best Da Hood scripts in Roblox? In this article, we will discuss the top five Da Hood script GUIs that are highly recommended for players. These GUIs offer features like aimlock, ESPs, auto-farms, and more, making your gameplay experience much more enjoyable. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive right into it!
Step 1: Accessing the Scripts To get started, you will need to access the scripts. First, click on the first link provided in the video description.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Organize Your Setup with Elgato Stream Deck Plus** </title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/brown-bird-pokemon/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/brown-bird-pokemon/</guid>
      <description>In today&amp;rsquo;s world of streaming and content creation, having a well-organized setup is essential. That&amp;rsquo;s where the Elgato Stream Deck Plus comes in. This new product from Elgato is a game-changer when it comes to organizing and assigning buttons and dials for all your streaming needs.
The Elgato Stream Deck Plus is essentially a large macro board that allows you to easily assign buttons and dials to any function you need.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Live Full Odds Shiny Lucario after 1,255 SRs! • Pokemon Sword</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/shiny-lucario-sword/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/shiny-lucario-sword/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing the exciting journey of capturing a shiny Lucario in Pokemon Sword. The process involves more than 1,255 SRs (soft resets) and showcases the thrill and dedication required to obtain this rare and shiny Pokemon. Join us as we delve into the steps taken to achieve this remarkable feat and explore the uniqueness of a shiny Lucario.
The Hunt Begins The video starts with the narrator expressing excitement and readiness for the hunt for a shiny Lucario.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Path of Exile: A Beginner&#39;s Guide to Using the Blood Altar</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-use-blood-altar-in-path-of-exile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-use-blood-altar-in-path-of-exile/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this guide, we will walk you through how to use the Blood Altar in Path of Exile. The Blood Altar is a unique feature in the game that allows players to capture and sacrifice animals in exchange for valuable crafting materials. If you&amp;rsquo;re new to the game or simply confused about this mechanic, don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!
Step 1: Finding the Blood Altar and the Beastmaster To start using the Blood Altar, you first need to locate the Beastmaster NPC.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Get the Wish-Ender Bow in 2023! Easy Updated Awoken Talisman Exotic Guide! [Destiny 2 Lightfall]</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-get-wish-ender-quest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-get-wish-ender-quest/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In the world of Destiny 2, the Wish-Ender bow is a highly sought-after exotic weapon. But obtaining it hasn&amp;rsquo;t always been an easy task. However, with the release of Season 22 in Destiny 2&amp;rsquo;s Lightfall, Bungie has made some changes to the wish Ender&amp;rsquo;s exotic quest to simplify the process. In this article, we will break down these changes and provide a step-by-step guide on how you can get your hands on the Wish-Ender bow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Spawn Tranq Arrows in Ark - A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-give-yourself-tranq-arrows-in-ark/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-give-yourself-tranq-arrows-in-ark/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will explore how to spawn tranq arrows in the game Ark: Survival Evolved using the GFI command. Tranq arrows are a valuable resource in the game as they allow players to tranquilize and tame dinosaurs. By following the instructions below, you will be able to obtain as many tranq arrows as you need. So let&amp;rsquo;s dive right in!
To spawn tranq arrows in Ark, you will need to use the GFI command.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Neverwinter In 2022: A Complete Leveling Revamp Review</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/neverwinter-mmo-cross-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/neverwinter-mmo-cross-platform/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Neverwinter is a popular action combat MMORPG set in the Dungeons and Dragons universe. Released in 2013 for PC, the game has seen growth in its player base over the years, especially after its console releases. Known for its voice-acted dialogue and a mix of both PvE and PvP content, Neverwinter offers a highly immersive and engaging gameplay experience. In this article, we will dive deep into the game&amp;rsquo;s recent leveling revamp and explore the changes made to the new player experience in 2022.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Titanfall 2 Cross Platform Play: A Stable and Functional Gaming Experience on Consoles**</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-titanfall-2-cross-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-titanfall-2-cross-platform/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the world of gaming, reuniting with an old favorite can be both thrilling and apprehensive. Fans of Titanfall 2, rejoice! As of June 4th, 2022, Titanfall 2 is back and fully playable on consoles. This is incredibly exciting news for pilots who have been waiting eagerly to dive back into the chaotic, futuristic battlefield. In this article, we will explore the state of Titanfall 2, its recent improvements, and the multiplayer experience on consoles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Azur Lane Destroyers Tier List: The Ultimate Guide</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/azur-lane-submarine-tier-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/azur-lane-submarine-tier-list/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be diving into the world of Azur Lane, a popular mobile game known for its ship-based gameplay. Today, we will be focusing on destroyers and creating a comprehensive tier list for these ships. Keep in mind that this tier list is based on our own experiences and opinions, so feel free to agree or disagree with it. Let&amp;rsquo;s get started!
Understanding the Tier List Before we delve into the individual ships, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand how the tier list is structured.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Convert Fortnite and CS:GO Sensitivity to Valorant, Siege, and Overwatch</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-to-overwatch-sensitivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-to-overwatch-sensitivity/</guid>
      <description>As gamers, we often find ourselves transitioning between different games, each with its unique mechanics and gameplay. One aspect that greatly affects our performance is sensitivity settings. Finding the perfect sensitivity can be crucial for accuracy and precision in games like Valorant, Siege, and Overwatch. In this article, we will explore how to convert sensitivity settings from Fortnite and CS:GO to these popular games and provide tips to help you optimize your gameplay.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Destiny 2: The Best Bows and How to Farm Them</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/destiny-2-accrued-redemption-bow-how-to-get/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/destiny-2-accrued-redemption-bow-how-to-get/</guid>
      <description>Destiny 2 offers a wide variety of weapons for players to choose from, but one weapon type that stands out among the rest is the bow. Bows can be incredibly powerful if used correctly, and they have become especially important in this season of Destiny 2 due to the only seasonal weapon mod for overload being bows.
In this article, we will discuss the best bows in the game and how to obtain them efficiently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Find Your Sensitivity in Overwatch 2: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-to-overwatch-sens/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-to-overwatch-sens/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article is an expert guide on finding the optimal sensitivity for Overwatch 2. If you&amp;rsquo;re struggling with your aim or want to improve your gameplay, this guide is for you.
When it comes to competitive gaming, having the right sensitivity is crucial for success. In Overwatch 2, finding the perfect sensitivity can greatly enhance your gameplay and give you a competitive edge. In this guide, we will walk you through the process of finding your ideal sensitivity in Overwatch 2 and explain the importance of DPI (dots per inch) and eDPI (effective DPI).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Ultimate Guide to Dominating Punisher Part 4 in Escape From Tarkov</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/tarkov-punisher/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/tarkov-punisher/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you&amp;rsquo;re an Escape From Tarkov player, you know that completing quests can be a challenging task. In this article, we will discuss the filthiest strategy for Punisher Part 4, a quest that requires taking out PMC&amp;rsquo;s on Shoreline and completing Silent Caliber with a suppressed shotgun. This strategy is based on tactical bush camping outside the Shoreline Resort and has been proven to be incredibly effective. So, without further ado, let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the details and learn how to dominate Punisher Part 4 in Escape From Tarkov.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ESPN Reporter Malika Andrews Allegedly Dating Co-Worker Dave McMenamin: Exploring the Rumors</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/who-is-malika-andrews-dating/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/who-is-malika-andrews-dating/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Recently, there has been a lot of buzz surrounding ESPN reporter Malika Andrews and her alleged secret relationship with her co-worker, Dave McMenamin. Despite being together for a year, the couple managed to keep their relationship under wraps, possibly because Andrews was still trying to establish herself in the industry. This surprising revelation has caused quite a stir on social media, leading many to question the authenticity of her public persona.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Find Your Sensitivity in Overwatch 2: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/overwatch-to-fortnite-sens/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/overwatch-to-fortnite-sens/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the world of competitive gaming, having the right sensitivity in your favorite first-person shooter game can make all the difference. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned player or a beginner, finding the optimal sensitivity in Overwatch 2 is crucial for improving your aim and overall gameplay. In this article, we will explore the importance of sensitivity, the difference between DPI and in-game sensitivity, and how to find the perfect balance for your needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Reset Chunks in Minecraft - The Ultimate Guide for a Fresh Start</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/minecraft-refresh-chunks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/minecraft-refresh-chunks/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready for a fresh start in Minecraft? In this guide, we will show you how to reset chunks in Minecraft and find the perfect location for your new base. With the release of Minecraft 1.17, it&amp;rsquo;s time to update and explore new possibilities. So let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and create a brand new world!
The Story So Far In the previous episode, we embarked on a big project - the Giant Panda Resort in the jungle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> WATCH SPORTS on IPTV in 2023: A Comprehensive Guide to Finding the Best IPTV Service</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/bestsolaris-stream/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/bestsolaris-stream/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As the prices of cable and satellite TV continue to skyrocket, more and more sports fans are cutting the cord and turning to IPTV (Internet Protocol Television) as their go-to streaming option. In this article, we will explore the world of IPTV and provide you with a detailed guide on how to watch sports on IPTV in 2023. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re looking for legal and free options or are willing to explore paid subscriptions, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Cross Platform Update: Dragon Ball Xenoverse 2 DLC 13 Review</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/cross-platform-dragon-ball-xenoverse/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/cross-platform-dragon-ball-xenoverse/</guid>
      <description>Dragon Ball Xenoverse 2 has just announced its DLC 13 update, and fans are buzzing with excitement. But amidst the hype over new characters, it&amp;rsquo;s clear that the focus should be on something else entirely - a cross-platform update. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the importance of cross-platform play and why it could breathe new life into this beloved game.
Key Points
The Two New Characters: DLC 13 introduces two new characters to the game - Super Saiyan Gogeta and Full Power Jiren.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Find Your Optimal Sensitivity in Overwatch 2</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-sensitivity-to-overwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-sensitivity-to-overwatch/</guid>
      <description>Sensitivity in video games can have a huge impact on your overall performance. It affects your aim, response time, and how quickly you can react to situations. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how to find your optimal sensitivity in Overwatch 2.
The Impact of Sensitivity Before we dive into the specifics, let&amp;rsquo;s understand the impact of sensitivity in gameplay. Sensitivity refers to the speed at which your in-game character or crosshair moves when you move your mouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Stream Your PS4 Games on Discord (Easy Method)</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/ps4-stream-discord/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/ps4-stream-discord/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a way to share your exciting PlayStation 4 gameplay with your friends on Discord? Look no further! In this article, we will guide you through an easy method to stream your PS4 games on Discord, allowing your friends to watch and even listen to the gameplay. So let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and get started!
Before we begin, make sure to follow the steps below:
Step 1: Visit PS Remote Play Website The first thing you need to do is visit the PS Remote Play website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Jump Force: A Review of the Manga Fighting Game in 2023</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-naruto-jumpforce-cross-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-naruto-jumpforce-cross-platform/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome back to Retro Rebound! In today&amp;rsquo;s video, we will be discussing the popular manga fighting game, Jump Force. Released in 2019, this game was highly anticipated as it combines characters from 15 different manga series, including Naruto, Dragon Ball, JoJo&amp;rsquo;s Bizarre Adventure, and more. However, since its release, there have been some significant changes and developments that have affected the game. In this article, we will take an in-depth look at Jump Force in 2023, exploring its gameplay, character roster, story mode, and overall quality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Convert Your Sensitivity from One Game to Another 2021: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-sens-to-csgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-sens-to-csgo/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article is a written transcript of the YouTube video titled &amp;ldquo;How to Convert Your Sensitivity from One Game to Another 2021!!&amp;rdquo; by CAZE GAMING.
If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever struggled with transferring your sensitivity settings from one game to another, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. It can be extremely difficult to achieve the same level of precision and accuracy when switching between games like CS:GO, Overwatch, and Valorant. Fortunately, there&amp;rsquo;s a simple and effective solution that can help you maintain consistency in your gameplay across multiple games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Stream PS4 on Discord: An Easy Method</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-stream-ps4-on-discord/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-stream-ps4-on-discord/</guid>
      <description>Are you a gamer who wants to share your PlayStation 4 (PS4) gameplay with your friends on Discord? Look no further! In this article, we will guide you on how to stream your PS4 on Discord using a simple and easy method. By following these steps, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to showcase your gaming skills and have your friends join in on the excitement. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive right in!
Step 1: Access PS Remote Play To begin, you need to access PS Remote Play, a tool that allows you to stream your PS4 gameplay on Discord.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Minecraft&#39;s Evolution on YouTube: From 2009 to Present</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/oldest-minecraft-youtubers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/oldest-minecraft-youtubers/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Minecraft, the popular sandbox game, has been captivating players for over a decade. Since its creation, Minecraft has made a significant impact on YouTube, with countless videos showcasing the game&amp;rsquo;s unique features and gameplay. In this article, we will take a trip down memory lane, exploring Minecraft&amp;rsquo;s history on YouTube and how it has evolved over the years.
The First Minecraft Video on YouTube: A Humble Beginning In May 2009, Minecraft was officially released to the public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> State of Play on Multiple Platforms: Conan Exiles 2022</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-conan-exiles-cross-platform-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-conan-exiles-cross-platform-2022/</guid>
      <description>Conan Exiles is a highly popular game that has attracted a dedicated player base across multiple platforms. In this article, we will be discussing the recent state of play for Conan Exiles on various platforms, focusing on the gameplay experience offered and the recent updates on consoles. We will also touch upon the challenges faced by Funcom, the game&amp;rsquo;s developer, when it comes to handling patches and ensuring a consistent experience across all platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Escape From Tarkov - Easy Guide to Finding Found In Raid Kinda Cowboy Hats for the Dressed To Kill Quest</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/dressed-to-kill-tarkov/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/dressed-to-kill-tarkov/</guid>
      <description>In this video, Acez EFT shows us an easy method to find the &amp;ldquo;kinda cowboy hats&amp;rdquo; needed for the Dressed To Kill quest in Escape From Tarkov. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or an experienced player, this guide will help you get these hats easily. Make sure to follow the step-by-step instructions and explore the different locations to maximize your chances of finding the hats. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and start our quest for the &amp;ldquo;kinda cowboy hats&amp;rdquo;!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Use Discord with Xbox and Connect the Voice Channel - Step by Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/discord-stream-via-xbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/discord-stream-via-xbox/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will guide you through the process of using Discord directly on your Xbox, allowing you to connect to the Discord voice channel and communicate seamlessly. By following the steps below, you will be able to link your Discord account to your Xbox and enjoy the convenience of using Discord while gaming on your console.
Step 1: Accessing Settings To begin, navigate to the settings on your Xbox.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Neverwinter in 2022: A Revamped Leveling Experience</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/neverwinter-cross-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/neverwinter-cross-platform/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Neverwinter is an action combat MMORPG set in the Dungeons and Dragons universe. Released on PC in 2013, the game has maintained a reasonable player base over the years. With console releases and a continuous flow of content updates, Neverwinter remains a highly driven MMO packed with voice-acted dialogue. In this article, we will explore the revamped leveling experience in Neverwinter in 2022 and see if it has improved.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PoE Blood Altar Beast Crafting &amp; Recipes Guide - How to Use the Blood Altar in Path of Exile</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-use-blood-altar-poe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-use-blood-altar-poe/</guid>
      <description>In the world of Path of Exile, understanding the mechanics behind the Blood Altar and beast crafting is essential for creating powerful items. In this comprehensive guide, we will explore how to effectively use the Blood Altar and delve into beast crafting recipes. Whether you are a seasoned player or new to the game, this guide will assist you in mastering this aspect of Path of Exile.
Navigating to the Menagerie To begin your journey into beast crafting, you must first know how to travel to the Menagerie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dragon Ball Xenoverse 2 DLC 13 Update: Cross Platform Coming Soon?</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/xenoverse-2-crossplay-pc-and-ps4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/xenoverse-2-crossplay-pc-and-ps4/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the world of Dragon Ball Xenoverse 2, exciting news has been announced regarding the much-anticipated DLC 13 update. While the update will bring in new characters like Super Saiyan Gogeta and Full Power Jiren, it seems that fans are more concerned about the lack of cross-platform support between PC and PS4. In this article, we will delve into the importance of cross-platform play, the potential impact it could have on the game&amp;rsquo;s longevity, and why Bandai, the game&amp;rsquo;s developer, should seriously consider implementing this feature.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Uber Atziri - Alluring Abyss: A Path of Exile Guide</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/poe-mortal-rage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/poe-mortal-rage/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will explore the mechanics and strategies for defeating Uber Atziri in the Alluring Abyss map in the popular game Path of Exile. Uber Atziri is a challenging boss encounter that requires careful planning and execution to overcome. We will discuss the key strategies for success, as well as tips on gearing and preparing for the fight. Read on to find out how to defeat this formidable foe and claim victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Jey Uso&#39;s Family: Discover the WWE Star&#39;s Wife and Children</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/does-jey-uso-have-a-wife/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/does-jey-uso-have-a-wife/</guid>
      <description>Ah, the world of professional wrestling, where larger-than-life characters captivate audiences with their incredible athleticism and captivating storylines. Among these stars is Jay Uso, whose real name is Joshua Samuel Fatu, a proud member of the renowned Anoa&amp;rsquo;i family and one-half of the legendary tag team, the Usos. But while Jay&amp;rsquo;s professional life is often in the limelight, he prefers to keep his personal life private. Today, we delve into the lesser-known aspects of Jay Uso&amp;rsquo;s family, including his wife and children.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Boros Soldiers: The Underrated Powerhouse</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/boros-soldier/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/boros-soldier/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome back, esteemed readers! Today, we will be diving into the world of Magic: The Gathering, specifically exploring the Boros Soldiers deck archetype. This powerful red and white deck has been flying under the radar, but trust me when I say that it is truly amazing. In this article, we will be analyzing the decklist, discussing strategies and synergies, and showcasing its performance in high-level gameplay. By the end of this article, you will understand why Boros Soldiers is a force to be reckoned with.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> In-Depth Guide on How to Differentiate Shadowless Pokemon TCG Cards from Unlimited Cards</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/pokemon-shadowless-cards/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/pokemon-shadowless-cards/</guid>
      <description>Introduction When it comes to collecting Pokemon trading cards, avid collectors and enthusiasts are always on the hunt for rare editions. One such distinction is between shadowed and shadowless Pokemon cards. In this comprehensive guide, we will delve into understanding the key differences between shadowed and shadowless cards, including their rarity and how to identify them.
Understanding the Rarity of Shadowless Pokemon Cards When the Pokemon trading card game (TCG) was initially printed, there were three variations: shadowless first edition, shadowless, and unlimited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HOW TO CONVERT YOUR SENSITIVITY FROM ONE GAME TO ANOTHER 2021!!</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/siege-to-fortnite-sens-converter/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/siege-to-fortnite-sens-converter/</guid>
      <description>Are you a gamer who likes to play different games and wants to have the same sensitivity settings across all games? If so, you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place. In this article, we will show you a super easy way to transfer your sensitivity settings from one game to another, so you can have the perfect sense in every game you play.
To achieve this, you will need to download an aim training game called AimLab.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Easily Convert Your Sensitivity from One Game to Another in 2021!</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-to-csgo-sensitivity-calculator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-to-csgo-sensitivity-calculator/</guid>
      <description>Are you a gamer who loves playing different games but struggles to find the perfect sensitivity in each game? Have you ever wondered how to transfer your sensitivity settings from one game to another effortlessly? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck! In this article, we will show you a super easy way to convert your sensitivity settings from one game to another, allowing you to have the same consistent sensitivity across all your favorite games.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PayDay 2 Multiplayer Tutorial: How to Play with Friends on Different Platforms</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/payday-2-cross-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/payday-2-cross-platform/</guid>
      <description>Are you a fan of PayDay 2 but struggling to play multiplayer with your friends, especially if they are on different platforms? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. In this tutorial, we will show you step-by-step how to play PayDay 2 multiplayer with friends, whether they are on the Epic Games Store or Steam.
Step 1: Access the Social Hub First, launch PayDay 2 and navigate to the main menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PayDay 2 Multiplayer Tutorial: How to Play with Friends on PC and PS4</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-payday-2-crossplay-pc-and-ps4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-payday-2-crossplay-pc-and-ps4/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to play PayDay 2 multiplayer with your friends, whether they&amp;rsquo;re on Epic or Steam? In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll guide you through the process of playing with friends on different platforms. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a new player or a seasoned veteran, our step-by-step instructions will make it easy for you to connect and enjoy the thrilling multiplayer experience PayDay 2 has to offer.
Step 1: Accessing the Social Hub To start, open up the PayDay 2 main menu and navigate to the Social Hub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> PoE Blood Altar Beastcrafting &amp; Recipes Guide - How to Use the Blood Altar in Path of Exile</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/poe-use-the-blood-altar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/poe-use-the-blood-altar/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will guide you through the process of using the Blood Altar in the Menagerie to perform Beastcrafting and unlock recipes in Path of Exile (PoE). Beastcrafting is a unique method of crafting in PoE that involves sacrificing beasts to the Blood Altar to obtain powerful items and gems. We will provide a step-by-step process on how to utilize the Blood Altar effectively and showcase a specific recipe for creating a 23% quality corrupted gem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A Way Out: The Ultimate Co-op Gaming Experience</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/way-out-cross-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/way-out-cross-platform/</guid>
      <description>Cooperative gaming has always been a favorite pastime for many gamers, providing an opportunity to bond with friends and overcome challenges together. From the days of high school to the present day, my friend and I have made it our mission to conquer every fun co-op game that comes our way. We&amp;rsquo;ve had some incredible experiences, but nothing compares to our recent adventure with a game called &amp;ldquo;A Way Out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is Monopoly Plus Cross Platform from PC? A Comprehensive Review </title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-monopoly-plus-cross-platform-from-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-monopoly-plus-cross-platform-from-pc/</guid>
      <description>Monopoly Plus is the official PC version of the popular board game Monopoly, but it comes with its fair share of issues. Developed by Ubisoft, it relies on Ubisoft Connect as its social service platform. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss why Monopoly Plus may not be the best choice for PC gamers and explore alternative options.
Bugs, Exploits, and Crashes One of the biggest drawbacks of Monopoly Plus is its numerous bugs and glitches.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> So I Tried Playing JUMP FORCE In 2023: A Review of the Definitive Manga Fighting Game</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/does-jump-force-have-cross-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/does-jump-force-have-cross-platform/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to Retro Rebound! In today&amp;rsquo;s video, we&amp;rsquo;re taking a trip back to 2019 to revisit JUMP FORCE, a game that was highly anticipated upon its release. With its unique concept of bringing together characters from 15 different manga series, including Dragon Ball, Naruto, One Piece, and more, JUMP FORCE had the potential to be the definitive manga fighting game. However, in 2023, is it still as exciting and enjoyable as it was before?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> In-Depth Guide: How to Determine if a Pokemon Card is Shadowless</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-tell-if-a-pokemon-card-is-shadowless/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-tell-if-a-pokemon-card-is-shadowless/</guid>
      <description>Introduction When collecting Pokemon TCG cards, it is important to distinguish between shadowed and shadowless cards. Shadowless cards are considered more rare and valuable than their shadowed counterparts. In this article, we will explore the key differences between shadowless and shadowed Pokemon cards. We will provide step-by-step instructions on how to identify shadowless cards, and discuss the rarity and value associated with these cards.
Understanding Shadowless Cards When Pokemon cards were first printed, there were three variations: shadowless first edition, shadowless, and unlimited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> [Hunt Showdown] How to Enable Crossplay on PS4 and Xbox One</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/hunt-showdown-crossplay-ps4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/hunt-showdown-crossplay-ps4/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to play Hunt Showdown with your friends on different platforms, such as PS4 and Xbox One, you may have encountered difficulties. The game does not have built-in crossplay functionality, but there is a workaround that allows players on different platforms to play together. In this article, we will guide you through the process of enabling crossplay and playing Hunt Showdown with your friends on PS4 and Xbox One.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Transfer Your Sensitivity from Fortnite to CS:GO in 2021!!</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-to-csgo-sensitivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-to-csgo-sensitivity/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling to find the perfect sensitivity in CS:GO after playing Fortnite? Transferring your sensitivity from one game to another can be a challenging and time-consuming task. Each game has its own unique sensitivity settings, making it difficult to achieve consistency across different titles. But don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we have a super easy solution for you!
To help you with this, we recommend downloading a free game called Aim Lab from Steam.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Warframe: Nitain Extract Farming 2020 Guide - How to Find Nitain Extract in Warframe</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/nitain-extract-farming-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/nitain-extract-farming-2019/</guid>
      <description>If you are a Warframe player, you know how important Nitain Extract is for crafting various items and equipment. This guide will teach you the best strategies and locations to farm Nitain Extract in 2020. We will go over the steps to optimize your farming and maximize your chances of obtaining this valuable resource.
1. Understanding Nitain Extract Nitain Extract is a rare resource in the game Warframe. It is used for crafting various Warframe blueprints, weapons, and other essential items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Stream Xbox Gameplay to Discord: A New Integration from Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/can-u-stream-discord-videos-on-xbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/can-u-stream-discord-videos-on-xbox/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re an Xbox user and love interacting with friends on Discord, we have exciting news for you. Microsoft has recently made improvements to the Discord integration on Xbox, allowing you to now stream your gameplay directly to your friends on Discord. In this article, we will discuss the steps to enable this feature, customization options, and its availability for different consoles.
Enabling Gameplay Streaming on Discord To start streaming your gameplay on Discord, follow these steps:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> In-Depth Guide: How to Identify Shadowless Pokemon TCG Cards from Unlimited Cards</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/what-is-shadowless-pokemon-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/what-is-shadowless-pokemon-card/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Pokemon TCG cards have become highly collectible items, and with their growing popularity, it&amp;rsquo;s essential for collectors to familiarize themselves with different card variations to ensure they are purchasing authentic and valuable ones. In this article, we will delve into the world of shadowless Pokemon cards, explaining what they are and how to tell them apart from unlimited cards.
Key Points The Difference Between Shadowed and Shadowless Pokemon Cards Rarity Levels: Shadowless First Edition, Shadowless, and Unlimited Identifying Shadowless Cards: Visual Clues Examining Onix and Bill Cards for Differences Key Details to Look For: Text Boldness and Energy Cost Placement Shadowless Cards: No Shadow on the Right-Hand Side The Easiest Way to Identify Shadowless Cards: The Bottom Print Trainers Cards: Differences in Text and Bottom Print Examining the Back of the Cards for Similarities Exception: Machamp Card with First Edition Stamp Visual Comparison of Shadowless and Unlimited Cards Now, let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the detailed step-by-step process of identifying shadowless Pokemon TCG cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> In-Depth Item Guide for Every Champion in Teamfight Tactics</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/scarra-best-tft-items/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/scarra-best-tft-items/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Teamfight Tactics is a popular game mode in League of Legends that requires strategic thinking and careful itemization. In this guide, we will take a closer look at the best item builds for each champion in the game. We will organize the guide by class, starting with Assassins and working our way through the list. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a new player or a seasoned veteran, this guide will provide you with valuable information to help you dominate the competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>**HOW TO RESET CHUNKS IN MINECRAFT - A GUIDE FOR A FRESH START**</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-refresh-chunks-minecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-refresh-chunks-minecraft/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will discuss the process of resetting chunks in Minecraft to start fresh and explore new biomes. With the upcoming release of Minecraft 1.17, it&amp;rsquo;s important to prepare our worlds for the new update and make the necessary adjustments. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re an experienced player or a beginner, this guide will walk you through the steps of using the MCA Selector to reset chunks and create a new base.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Shaking Up Teller - A Comprehensive Prapor Task Guide in Escape From Tarkov</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/shaking-up-teller-tarkov/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/shaking-up-teller-tarkov/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this comprehensive guide, we will walk you through the steps of completing the &amp;ldquo;Shaking Up Teller&amp;rdquo; task given by Prapor in the popular game Escape From Tarkov. This guide will provide you with detailed instructions and key information to successfully complete the task. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!
Task Overview The objective of the &amp;ldquo;Shaking Up Teller&amp;rdquo; task is to obtain a valuable item located in dorm room 203 on the Customs map and then safely extract with it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Co-Op - No Server Needed! - Multi-player Options (Update)</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/conan-exiles-crossplay-ps4-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/conan-exiles-crossplay-ps4-pc/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will explore the different ways to play Conan Exiles and discuss a red flag related to privacy that needs to be addressed. Whether you prefer single-player/co-op or online server play, this guide will provide you with step-by-step instructions on how to get started. Additionally, we will highlight some important considerations to protect your privacy while playing the game.
Single Player/Co-Op Mode To begin playing Conan Exiles, you have two options: play online or choose the single player/co-op mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Stream PS4 Gameplay to Discord: An Easy Method</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-stream-ps4-gameplay-to-discord/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/how-to-stream-ps4-gameplay-to-discord/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking for a way to stream your PS4 gameplay on Discord? Look no further! In this article, we will guide you through a simple step-by-step process to help you easily stream your PS4 gameplay to Discord. Not only will you be able to showcase your gaming skills, but your friends in the call will also be able to hear the sound coming from your PS4. Let&amp;rsquo;s get started!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Nexus Blitz Tier List: A Comprehensive Guide for 2021</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/nexus-blitz-tier-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/nexus-blitz-tier-list/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will be discussing the gameplay and strategies for the Nexus Blitz mode in League of Legends. Specifically, we will focus on the mid lane and bot lane roles and provide tips and insights to help you excel in these positions. Whether you are new to Nexus Blitz or looking to improve your performance, this guide will provide valuable information to enhance your gameplay.
Introduction to Nexus Blitz Laning Nexus Blitz is unique in its gameplay, offering a 1v1 mid lane and a 2v2 bot lane experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Update 3.0 Dev Q&amp;A Recap - Everything You Need to Know About Conan Exiles</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/conan-exiles-cross-platform-ps4-pc/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/conan-exiles-cross-platform-ps4-pc/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In a recent Q&amp;amp;A livestream, the Conan Exiles developers discussed the highly-anticipated update 3.0, addressing some of the most pressing questions about the upcoming Age of Sorcery expansion. In this article, we will provide a detailed recap of the stream, covering key points, updates, and future plans for the game.
Monetization and Test Environment Before diving into the specifics of update 3.0, the developers addressed the issue of monetization in the test environment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ESPN Reporter Malika Andrews Under Fire For Alleged Secret Relationship with White NBA Reporter Dave McMenamin</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/malika-andrews-boyfriend/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/malika-andrews-boyfriend/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Prominent ESPN reporter, Malika Andrews, has found herself at the center of controversy after rumors began circulating about her alleged secret relationship with fellow NBA reporter, Dave McMenamin. The news has sparked a frenzy on social media, with fans expressing shock and amusement at the unexpected pairing. In this article, we will explore the details of this alleged relationship and discuss the reactions it has garnered.
The Surprising Revelation According to recent reports, Malika Andrews and Dave McMenamin have been romantically involved for about a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is Monopoly Plus Cross-Platform? A Comprehensive Review</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-monopoly-cross-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-monopoly-cross-platform/</guid>
      <description>Monopoly Plus is a popular game that offers a unique digital experience of the classic board game. While it has gained a significant following, there are some key issues with the game that we will discuss in this article. One major concern is the host connection system, where if the host leaves the game, the entire game ends abruptly. This can be frustrating for players who are in the middle of a winning streak or enjoying a competitive match.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Noted Sensitivity: Exploring the Secrets of a Skilled Player</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/noted-sensitivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/noted-sensitivity/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will dive into the sensitivity settings of a skilled player known as Noted. He is a former professional player in both CJ and Apex, and his expertise is highly regarded in the gaming community. We will discuss his unique sensitivity curve and the impact it has on his gameplay. Additionally, we will explore the training routines that have contributed to his exceptional aiming skills. So, let&amp;rsquo;s begin our journey to uncover the secrets of Noted&amp;rsquo;s sensitivity and aim.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> We Finally Did It! Boros Army Dominates All Star Tower Defense</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/boros-soldier-men/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/boros-soldier-men/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to witness the power of the Boros Army in All Star Tower Defense? In this exciting gameplay video, SnowRBX and his hardcore Snow Squad take on the challenge of building an unbeatable army. With the help of Supreme Felipe and Simply icyt, they aim to dominate the leaderboard and achieve the highest wave possible. Join them on their epic journey as they showcase the strategies and units they use to create an unstoppable force.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Andre the Giant&#39;s Daughter: A Heartbreaking Story of Neglect and Abandonment</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/jean-christensen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/jean-christensen/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the early 90s, the world was captivated by the larger-than-life persona of Andre the Giant, the most recognizable professional wrestler of his time. However, behind the glamorous facade, there was a heartbreaking story of neglect and abandonment that unfolded. This article delves into the emotional journey of Andre&amp;rsquo;s daughter, Robin, and the pain she experienced as her famous father remained absent from her life. Join us as we explore the complexities of their relationship and the impact it had on both their lives.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Conan Exiles Crossplay: Uniting PS4, PC, and Xbox Players</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/conan-exiles-crossplay-xbox-ps4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/conan-exiles-crossplay-xbox-ps4/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing the exciting news surrounding Conan Exiles and the potential implementation of cross-platform play. This highly anticipated feature would allow players on different platforms, such as PC, PS4, and Xbox, to join forces and play together. We will delve into the details of cross-platform play, its implications, and the potential benefits it brings to the Conan Exiles community. Additionally, we will explore other features that are currently in development, including character customization options and improvements to the game&amp;rsquo;s story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Convert Fortnite to CS:GO in 7 minutes**</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-convert-to-csgo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-convert-to-csgo/</guid>
      <description>Written by an expert copywriter
Introduction In this article, we will explore how to convert models and textures from Fortnite to CS:GO. If you&amp;rsquo;ve ever wanted to bring Fortnite assets into the world of Counter-Strike, this is the guide for you. By following these steps, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to seamlessly integrate Fortnite models into the CS:GO environment. So let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and get started!
Key Points to Remember Before we begin, let&amp;rsquo;s outline the key points we need to keep in mind throughout the conversion process:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 5 Best Minecraft Mansion Seeds - Explore Epic Mansions in Minecraft 1.11</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/best-minecraft-1.11-mansion-seeds/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/best-minecraft-1.11-mansion-seeds/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to discover some amazing Minecraft mansion seeds in the latest update? In this article, we will share with you five incredible seeds for Minecraft mansions in version 1.11. We&amp;rsquo;ll provide you with the coordinates and sources for each seed, ensuring you have everything you need to embark on your mansion adventure. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and explore these exciting Minecraft mansion seeds together!
Seed 1: A Mansion Near Spawn If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a mansion close to your spawn point, this seed is perfect for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AK117: The Secretly META Weapon in COD Mobile</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/ak117-cod-mobile-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/ak117-cod-mobile-stats/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the world of Call of Duty: Mobile, there are always a handful of weapons that dominate the meta. These weapons, commonly referred to as META weapons, are the go-to choices for players looking to gain an advantage in gunfights. However, there is one weapon that has been flying under the radar, quietly proving itself to be just as powerful as its META counterparts. That weapon is the AK117.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Ultimate Guide to Dark Tier List in Granblue Fantasy</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/dark-tier-list-gbf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/dark-tier-list-gbf/</guid>
      <description>Granblue Fantasy is a popular mobile game that offers various elements for players to choose from. In this article, we will focus on the Dark element, which is widely considered one of the most versatile and affordable elements to build in the game. We will explore the key units and skills that make Dark a preferred choice for many players, as well as its strengths and weaknesses. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a new player or a seasoned veteran, this guide will provide valuable insights on maximizing your Dark element team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 10 Thrilling Games Like DEAD BY DAYLIGHT You Should Try!</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/games-youll-like-if-you-like-dead-by-daylight/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/games-youll-like-if-you-like-dead-by-daylight/</guid>
      <description>Horror fans are a unique group of individuals who require a certain level of fear and excitement to truly immerse themselves in a game. The wrong monster or a lackluster experience can ruin the immersive experience that horror gamers crave. That&amp;rsquo;s where the rise of asymmetric multiplayer games in the horror genre comes into play. One such game that stands out is DEAD BY DAYLIGHT, a game that allows players to step into the boots of iconic horror movie villains and experience the thrill of being the villain themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Free New Blue Emblem and Helios Crown Limited Time Emblem</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/new-blue-emblem-destiny/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/new-blue-emblem-destiny/</guid>
      <description>Unlock Exclusive Emblems in Destiny 2
Destiny 2 players, rejoice! Bungie has made some changes to the way Bungie Rewards are redeemed, giving you the chance to earn exclusive emblems for your Guardian. In this article, we will guide you through the process of claiming the new Blue Emblem and the Helios Crown emblem, available for a limited time.
Linking Your Bungie.net Account to Bungie Store To start off, you will need to link your bungie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Monopoly Plus - A Comprehensive Review of Main Issues and Gameplay Experience</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-monopoly-plus-cross-platform/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-monopoly-plus-cross-platform/</guid>
      <description>Monopoly Plus is a popular game with a decent gameplay experience, but it also has some key issues that need to be addressed. In this article, we will discuss the main problems encountered in Monopoly Plus and provide an in-depth review of its gameplay.
Host Connection System - A Game-Ender One of the major issues in Monopoly Plus is the host connection system. If the host of the game decides to leave, the entire game abruptly ends.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Path of Exile Delve: A Comprehensive Guide to Fossil Locations &amp; Farming</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/sanctified-fossil/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/sanctified-fossil/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this guide, we will explore the world of Path of Exile Delve and provide you with a comprehensive strategy for finding and farming various types of fossils. Fossils are valuable items used for crafting and trading within the game. We will discuss the different types of fossils, their locations, and how to efficiently farm them.
Understanding Fossil Locations
Fossils are primarily found in the darkness inside areas that are off the crawler&amp;rsquo;s path.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> So I tried playing JUMP FORCE In 2023: A Look Back at the Anime Fighter</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-jump-force-cross-play/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/is-jump-force-cross-play/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to Retro Rebound! In today&amp;rsquo;s video, we&amp;rsquo;re diving back into JUMP FORCE, a game that was released in 2019. When it was announced, it felt like a can&amp;rsquo;t-miss anime fighter, as it pulled characters from 15 different manga series. With JoJo, Dragon Ball, One Piece, Naruto, and more all in one place, JUMP FORCE had the potential to be the definitive manga fighting game. However, support for the game was dropped relatively quickly, leading to some interesting developments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Easier Jedi Fallen Order Cutscene Glitch!! Learn How to Skip Cutscenes and Speed Up Gameplay 10x </title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/jedi-fallen-order-how-to-skip-cutscenes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/jedi-fallen-order-how-to-skip-cutscenes/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of sitting through lengthy cutscenes while playing Jedi Fallen Order? Well, I&amp;rsquo;ve got some good news for you! In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing an easier way to activate a cutscene glitch that allows you to skip cutscenes and speed up gameplay by 10 times! Whether you&amp;rsquo;re playing on PlayStation or PC with a keyboard and mouse or a PS5 or PS4 controller, this glitch will work for you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Find Your Perfect Mouse Sensitivity for Any Game</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/sensitivity-overwatch-to-fortnite/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/sensitivity-overwatch-to-fortnite/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Mouse sensitivity is a crucial variable that can greatly impact your aim in gaming. A small adjustment to your sensitivity can make a dramatic difference in your accuracy. In this article, we will explore the process of finding the perfect mouse sensitivity that feels instinctive to you, allowing you to aim effortlessly and improve your overall performance in any game.
Understanding the Importance of Sensitivity When your sensitivity is too high, you may find yourself over-aiming, constantly correcting your Crosshair&amp;rsquo;s position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Find Your Sensitivity in Overwatch 2: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-sens-to-overwatch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/fortnite-sens-to-overwatch/</guid>
      <description>In the world of competitive gaming, finding the perfect sensitivity for your aim can make all the difference between victory and defeat. Overwatch 2, the highly popular team-based shooter game, is no exception. In this article, we will delve into the intricacies of finding your sensitivity in Overwatch 2, offering a step-by-step process to help you achieve optimal settings.
Before we dive into the details, let&amp;rsquo;s explain some basic terms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Find Your Perfect Sensitivity in Overwatch 2</title>
      <link>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/overwatch-to-fortnite-sensitivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gameinstants.github.io/posts/overwatch-to-fortnite-sensitivity/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to gaming, having the right sensitivity is crucial in order to perform at your best. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or a seasoned player, finding the ideal sensitivity can greatly impact your gameplay. In this article, we will discuss the importance of sensitivity in Overwatch 2 and guide you on how to find your perfect sensitivity for optimal performance.
Understanding Sensitivity and DPI Before we delve into finding the perfect sensitivity, let&amp;rsquo;s first understand the two key terms: Sensitivity and DPI.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
